Kung Fu Panda 4 is a animation, family, action film directed by Mike Mitchell.
Po is gearing up to become the spiritual leader of his Valley of Peace,
but also needs someone to take his place as Dragon Warrior.
As such, he will train a new kung fu practitioner for the spot and will encounter a
villain called the Chameleon who conjures villains from the past.
Po (voice), played by Jack Black.
Zhen (voice), played by Awkwafina.
The Chameleon (voice), played by Viola Davis.
Shifu (voice), played by Dustin Hoffman.
Li (voice), played by Bryan Cranston.
Mr. Ping (voice), played by James Hong.
Kung Fu Panda 4 is a 2024 American animated martial arts comedy film directed by Mike
Mitchell and written by Darren Lemke, Jonathan Aibel and Glenn Berger.
The fourth film in the Kung Fu Panda franchise, it
was produced by DreamWorks Animation.
It features Jack Black, Bryan Cranston, James Hong, Ian McShane, and
Dustin Hoffman reprising their roles from the previous films.
In the film, Po—who must find and train his successor as the new Dragon Warrior—teams up with fox bandit Zhen to defeat
evil sorceress The Chameleon, who plans to steal the kung-fu abilities of all deceased masters in China.
DreamWorks announced the fourth film in August 2022, with Mitchell, Stephanie Ma Stine, and
Huntley attached as director, co-director, and producer, respectively, by April 2023.
In December 2023, most of the main voice cast, along with the return of
Aibel and Berger as writers and co-producers, were confirmed.
Lemke's involvement was confirmed in February 2024.
Composer Hans Zimmer, who had scored for the previous three installments,
returned as composer alongside frequent collaborator Steve Mazzaro.
Kung Fu Panda 4 premiered at the AMC 14 Theater at The Grove in Los Angeles on March 3, 2024, and
was theatrically released in the United States on March 8 by Universal Pictures.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics and was commercially successful, grossing $547.7 million
worldwide on an $85 million budget, outgrossing its predecessor to become the ninth-highest-grossing film of 2024.
The film received three nominations at the 52nd Annie Awards and one
nomination at the 52nd Saturn Awards for Best Animated Feature.
The film explores themes of martial arts, kung fu, china, villain, sequel.
The tone is lighthearted.